Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Records 6185
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Records
1970-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition
6185
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Records.
5837738
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 24, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6185 P: Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Photographs 6185 PUBS: Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Publications 6185/001: Tompkins County Labor Coalition Health and Safety Topical Files
Work environment; Work environment -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Work environment -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Industrial hygiene; Industrial hygiene -- New York (State); Industrial hygiene -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Industrial hygiene -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Industrial hygiene -- Salt mines and mining -- New York (State); Industrial hygiene -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Industrial hygiene -- Employment -- Law and legislation -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Environmental responsibility -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Environmental responsibility -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Environmental responsibility -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Industrial safety -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Plant shutdowns -- Economic aspects -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Plant shutdowns -- Economic aspects -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Unfair labor practices -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Unfair labor practices -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Working class; Workers' compensation -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Workers' compensation -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Workers' compensation -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Workers' compensation -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Strikes and lockouts -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Strikes and lockouts -- New York (State) -- Cortland County; Tompkins County -- Officials and employees; Cortland County -- Officials and employees; Tompkins-Cortland Labor Coalition; American Postal Workers Union. Local 1151 (Ithaca, N.Y.) -- Archives; Ben & Jerry's (Firm) -- Archives; Brewer-Titchener Corporation, Cortland, N.Y. -- Archives; Cargill, Inc. -- Archives; Central Labor Council (Ithaca, N.Y.) -- Archives; Cornell University -- Employees -- Archives; Imperial Food Products. Plant (Hamlet, N.C.) -- Fire, 1991 -- Archives; Ithaca City School District (Ithaca, N.Y.) -- Archives; Ithaca Post Office (Ithaca, N.Y.) -- Archives; Lakeside Nursing Home -- Archives; Midstate Central Labor Council -- Archives; New York (State) Dept. of Labor -- Archives; New York (State) Public Employment Relations Board -- Archives; Smith-Corona Inc. -- Archives; Tompkins-Cortland Labor Coalition --Archives
5837738
- 2003 meetings (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence, meeting agendas, copies of "Union City News"
- 2002 MCLC meetings (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Meeting minutes, correspondence, meeting agendas
- 2001 MCLC meetings (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Affiliation Material, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Correspondence, constitution, charter application, memoranda, news clippings, and pamphlet concerning the affiliation of the Mid-State Central Labor Council (Labor Coalition) with the New York State AFL-CIO.
- AFL-CIO Organizing Institute, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Literature, information on Apprenticeship Program, Training Schedule, Application to the Institute.
- Ames Department Store Layoffs, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Correspondence and news clippings concerning department store layoffs.
- 1996 Annual Meeting, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Photographs, financial report, correspondence, news clippings, newsletters, press releases, grant proposal, resolution, meeting agendas and minutes, and notes from annual meetings
- Annual Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  City of Ithaca proclamation, annual reports, financial report, tax forms, handouts, news clippings presented at the 1991 annual meeting of the Tompkins/Cortland Labor Coalition (TCLC)
- Annual report, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Constitution and by-laws, phone and address directory, Steering Committee nomination list, attendance list, financial statements, annual reports for 1991 & 1992
- Annual report, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Annual report, tax forms, financial report, correspondence, yearly dues report, annual membership meeting announcement.
- Annual report, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Association for Union Democracy, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Correspondence
- Behavior Based Training, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Literature, training material, booklet - "Warning! Behavior Based Safety Can Be Hazardous to Your Health and Safety Program!"
- Ben and Jerry's Foundation, 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Grant proposals, correspondence, newspaper clippings.
- Brown Lung Association, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Newspaper clippings
- Building Codes, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Book "New York State Energy Conservation Construction Code", copy of "Official Compilation of Codes Rules & Regulations", other documentation.
- Building Trades Project, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Maps, City of Oswego - Motions, resolutions and notices, newspaper clippings, flyers, correspondence.
- Buttons, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Correspondence about buttons.
- Cargill Strike Support, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Newspaper clippings, petitions, rally permits, correspondence, telephone lists, meeting minutes, flyers.
- Cartoons (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Labor cartoons.
- Central New York Labor Federation, AFL-CIO Board, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Meeting agendas, minutes and correspondence.
- Child Care - Cortland County, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Flyer and correspondence.
- Chuck Wymms, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, notes, research articles. Labor cartoon, copy of Local 97 Reporter, computer disk included with some documentation about the Lakeside settlement.
- City Funding History, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, proposals, flyers, legislation, Ad-Hoc Committee reports.
- City of Ithaca - Funded Position., 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Employment Maintenance Legislation, correspondence, job evaluation, criteria for funding of positions, news clippings on layoffs & shutdowns, Proposals for funding for new Labor Position.
- City of Ithaca - Grant. report, funding requests., 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, e-mails, Service Agreements, Guidelines & Criteria for Funding, cash flow report, funding requests.
- City of Ithaca - Grant., 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Correspondence,funding requests, recommendations.
- City of Ithaca - Grant, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Guidelines & Criteria, Service Agreement, funding proposal, correspondence, approval of funding.
- City of Ithaca, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  1997-1998 budget, Guidelines & Criteria, correspondence, service funding proposal, Service Agreement, contract for services report, accomplishments of 1996, Common Council review of budget request, flyers.
- City of Ithaca - Grant., 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, grant information sheet, service agreement, resolution of funding.
- City of Ithaca - Grant, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Survey, flyers, funding proposal, copy of FYI newspaper, copy of The Working Press, newspaper clippings on Smith Corona, newspaper clippings on death of Suit-Kote worker, grant approval correspondence, meeting notes from Human Services Committee, funding requests, addendum to the grant proposal, Service Contract, 1990-1991 projected budget.
- CLC [Central Labor Council]--Surveys (pt.1), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Explanation of how survey is done. Copies of survey answers and correspondence.
- CLC [Central Labor Council]--Surveys (pt.2), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Copies of survey answers and correspondence.
- Collective Bargaining, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Collective Bargaining.Collective bargaining report - Standing Committee on Labor
- Common Sense Economics, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Books dealing with economics, "Common Sense Economics", "Wage Gap: Organizing Kit", "Tax Fairness: Organizing Kit"
- Community Loan Fund, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Newspaper clipplings, correspondence
- Concerned University Employees (C.U.E.), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Parking poll, C.U.E. tips newspaper, news clippings about the new parking fees at Cornell University.
- Constitution and By-Laws (changes), 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Preamble, revised constitution and by-laws, Coordinator's report on by-law changes.
- Constitution (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Master copy of the Constitution of the Mid-State Central Labor Coalition, AFL-CIO.
- Consultation, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Booklet "Consultation Services for the Employer"
- Contract information, 1991-1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  1991 Sylabus, 1996 Ithaca Teachers Association contract
- Coordinator, 1991-2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Annual retreat agenda, job announcements for Coordinator position, Labor Coalition survey results, Coordinator evaluation, correspondence, job descriptions of Coordinator and Office Manager.
- Correspondence - Cortland, 1970-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Newspaper clippings about Cortland County businesses, correspondence, interview notes, meeting minutes, membership lists, booklet about "Brockway"
- Correspondence - Steering Committee, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Correspondence, staff time allotment sheets, budget correspondence.
- Correspondence - TCLC, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Correspondence - TCLC, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Disability - (ADA) American With Disabilities Act, 1990-2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Literature, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, correspondence, Executive Summary of Compliance Manual Section 92, copy of FYI issue dealing with ADA (Sept. 1992), resource information for Social Security Disability, several books: "The Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990", "The Americans with Disabilities Act: Your Employment...", "The Americans with Disabilities Act: Questions and Answers", "The Americans with Disabilities Act: Your Responsibilities as an Employer", Ability You Can Bank On", "Fighting for the Right of Disabled Employees", several booklets published by Program on Employment and Disability, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell Univ.
- Discrimination -- Employment (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Pamphlets - "Education Discrimination", "Employment Discrimination, Information for the Private Sector and State and Local Governments"
- Drug Testing Information, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Information booklet, correspondence, newspaper articles, copies of legislation, "Negotiating Contract Language"
- Dues -- 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Due sheets for members
- Dues -- 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Constitution and By-Laws (copy), due sheets noting member payment
- Dues -- 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Due sheets from organizations and updated directory information on members, membership lists, correspondence
- Election Information, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Election stickers, newspaper clippings, candidate information.
- Election Information - Barbara Lifton, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Barbara Lifton, Newspaper clippings, campaign flyers, campaign information, invitations, posters, e-mail, and biography information.
- Election Information - Candidates, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Candidates, Newspaper clippings, correspondence, campaign ads, candidate survey, campaign flyers.
- Election Information - General, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  GeneralNewspaper clippings from before and after election day, e-mails, receipts, correspondence, election posters, candidate survey, campaign ads and flyers, bumper stickers.
- Election Information - General, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Newspaper clippings, campaign ads, correspondence.
- Election Information - General, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  GeneralCampaign ads, campaign stickers, newspaper clippings, correspondence.
- Environmental (Local), 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Map of New York State with toxic dumps marked, pamphlet "Campaign for Cleaner Corporations", booklet "The Plain English Guide to the Clean Air Act", correspondence, Earth Day action checklist for local Unions and Labour Councils.
- Events -- TCLC, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, meeting announcements, meeting agendas, meeting minutes, newspaper clippings, copy of "Suggestion Constitution for the Tompkins County Central Labor Council"
- Family and Medical Leave, 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  FYI issue from Sept. 1997, research articles, copy of "Your Rights Under the Family and Medical Leave Act of 1993", newspaper clippings, fact sheets, FYI issue from Dec 1993, copy of FMLA Law
- Federation for Industrial Retention & Renewal (FIRR), 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Policy, dues policy, organization structure documents, by-laws, member list, Directors report, copies of "News" (their newsletter).
- Fingerlakes Independence Center (FLIC) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Pamphlets and correspondence.
- Fiscal Policy Institute, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Tax Equity Training agenda and information, newspaper clippings, business card for a Fiscal Policy Analyst from the Institute, booklets: "The Fair Tax Guide for New York", "Special Revenue Report I & II", "Too Much for Too Few", "Brother, Can You Spare a Dime?"
- "Freedom of Information Government Law", "Your Right to Federal Records", misc., 1981-2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Freedom of Information"Using the Freedom of Information Act", "Your Right to Know: New York State's Open Government Law", "Your Right to Federal Records", newspaper clippings
- General Mailing List Guidelines (TCLC), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Document approved by the Steering Committee
- Graduate Advocacy Organization (GAO), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Copy of "The Grad Grind" newsletter
- Graphics & Cartoons (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Examples of worker safety cartoons and graphic examples for handouts and flyers.
- Grants, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Correspondence and grant applications
- Hamlet Fire, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Information on the plant fire in Hamlet, NC, at the Imperial Food Products, pamphlet "The Impact of the Imperial Food Products Fire: One Year Later", notes, newspaper clippings, papers written by Carl Feuer and Robin Whittlesey (of TCLC), about "Racism in the Workplace" and "The New Slavery", flyers
- Health and Safety Workshops for Asian Workforce at Cornell (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Handouts and correspondence pertaining to the the workshop
- Health Care information (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Material comparing American health care with Canadian health care programs.
- Health Insurance - TCLC, 1990-2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Privacy Notice, health care change pamphlets, provider lists, consumer guide to NY HMO's, Service Employee Benefit Fund - plan summary, correspondence, insurance forms, dental coverage information, newspaper clippings.
- Health Insurance information, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Newspaper "Consumers' Guide to New York's Managed Care Bill of Rights".Copy of "Q&A, Recent Changes in Health Care Law", put out by Dept. of Labor, "Health Benefits Under the Consolidated Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act (COBRA)" by US Dept. of Labor.
- Hiring -- Coordinator, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Job descriptions, application letters, hiring announcement, funding allocation, correspondence.
- Hiring -- Health & Safety Trainer, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Applications, reference letters, job postings, resumes.
- Hiring -- Health & Safety Trainer letter, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Resumes, job description, interview training material, correspondence, job offer letter.
- Information & Referral, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Personal information and referral information about people asking TCLC for help with job related problems, phone conversation notes, correspondence.
- Institute for Local Self-Reliance, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Publications by the Insitute
- Ithaca College -- Joint All College Health and Safety Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Joint All College Health and Safety Committee Meeting minutes, organization notes, and correspondence
- Ithaca Gun Displacement Information, 1982-1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Employee list, survey drafts, survey final copy, survey answers, financial reports, newspaper clipping, Union agreement.
- Ithaca Gun Displacement Survey, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Survey Completed survey sheets
- Ithaca Gun Social Cost Analysis, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Cost analysis, corrrespondence, statistics reports, computer disk (5-1/4") [unlabelled], St. Paul Jobs Impact Statement and correspondence.
- Jobs with Justice, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Cleveland Jobs with Justice, Coalition by-laws, sample letters calling meetings, sample Steering Committee agenda, sample minutes, miscellaneous
- Labor & Environment Conference (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Newspaper clippings, conference materials, correspondence
- Labor Alerts (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Information flyers printed to "Alert" local unions of labor related issues.
- Labor-Corporate Research, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Public company information sites - listing for corporate researchers
- Labor Day Picnic, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Organizing notes, flyers, financial information, correspondence, "Friend of Labor Award" information, Labor Day 2002 toolkit, worship resource book, newspaper clippings.
- Labor Day Picnic, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  "Friend of Labor Award" information, correspondence, flyers for 2000 Labor Day celebration.
- Labor Day Picnic, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, flyers, award information (Friend of Labor, Mother Jones, Goat of Labor, Joe Hill), planning information, newspaper clippings, receipts.
- Labor Day Picnic, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, flyers, newspaper clippings, award information (Friend of Labor, Mother Jones, Goat of Labor, Joe Hill)
- Labor Day Picnic, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Labor Day Picnic Flyers, correspondence, newspaper clippings, award information (Friend of Labor, Mother Jones, Goat of Labor, Joe Hill), picnic preparation correspondence, agenda, prize winner information, music information, photos, labor song sheets (words and music).
- Labor Education Committee, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Labor - Environment, 1994-1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Newspaper and magazine articles, "NYS Labor & Environment Network: 1994 Plan of Action", "Jobs and the Environment", published by Public Health Institute and the Labor Institute, copy of resolution dealing with hazardous exposures and the creation of Neighborhood Hazard Prevention Committee, in Passic County, New Jersey.
- Labor history - New York, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Issue of Public Employee Press celebrating 40th Anniversary of District Council 37 - the largest public employee union in any city of the nation.
- Labor issues, 1980-1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Newspaper clippings, newspaper & magazine articles
- Labor - Local, 1985-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Labor Alert newsletter, notes, correspondence, newspaper clippings, letters to the editor.
- Labor news for working families, 1987-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Flyers, newspaper clippings, correspondence with important labor news.
- Labor notes, Information/Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Copy of "Labor Notes" publication, correspondence about its creation, correspondence on Multi-Union Coalitions.
- Labor Party, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Certification forms, correspondence.
- Lawyers, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Handwritten references to lawyers names and addresses, correspondence.
- Leaflets (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Examples of leaflets used in worker safety and information for new leaflets.
- Legislation -- Local (Box 4, Folder 22)
  "Draft"of Labor Policies for the City of Ithaca, "Local Policy Options Benefiting Labor".
- Lesbian & Gay workers (Box 4, Folder 23)
  workers Pamphlets on worker rights
- Letter to the Editor, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Correspondence about letters, copies of letters, and newsclippings of letters.
- Maps, 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Miscellaneous maps giving directions to labor events,many are undated for Cortland and Ithaca area.
- Media Lists, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Lists of television, radio and newspaper names, addresses & phone numbers.Addresses for letters to editors for local and regional newspapers.
- Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Attendence sheet for year, correspondence about meetings, Labor Coalition - Schuyler County Membership List.
- Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Correspondence and meeting minutes for various meetings for the year, 1992 proposed budget, sign in sheets for members, meeting agendas.
- Meetings, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Correspondence, meeting minutes, role call sheets, meeting agendas, 1989 schedule of meetings for the year.
- Membership Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Committee Correspondence between TCLC and possible new members.
- Membership Lists (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Lists of Unions and individuals names, addresses, and phone numbers.
- Membership survey report, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Survey questions, survey result report.
- Memos - Housing Issues, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Correspondence, meeting notes, proposals for housing solutions, meeting invitations.
- NAFTA, 1992-2002 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Union pamphlets, Union ads, petitions to Congressman Walsh, "Fast Track" flyers, UAW Administrative Letter, letters from Congressman Boehlert, Walsh, political cartoons, newspaper clippings, correspondence
- NAFTA - Anti -- Plant Closing Worksheets, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Newspaper clippings about Triangle Steel, demonstration flyers, information sheets, "Anti-NAFTA Phoners Rap Sheet", correspondence, Legislator list
- National Immigration Law Center, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  "Emma Lazarus Fund Grantees" memo, correspondence, booklets onhiring and job discrimination.
- Negotiations -- Tompkins-Seneca-Tioga BOCES, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Negotiation notebook, training schedule & agenda, negotiation training information, information on the Taylor Law
- Negotiations -- UAW Local 1774, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  1989 Brewer Tichener Negotiation notebook, Union contract campaign plan, copy of Collective Bargaining Law, ILR Career Services information on WISP
- New Alliance, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, flyers - information on forming New York Alliance
- New Alliance, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- New Alliance -- CA tour, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Notes and memos on CA tour. Correspondence and workshop information.
- New York Healthy Schools Network (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Newsletter and correspondence
- New York Labor Policy -- History, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- New York State Dept. of Labor -- Grants, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Local Initiative grant paperwork, correspondence, Building Trades Proposal paperwork, Contract Signature sheets
- New York State Dept. of Labor -- Hazard Abatement Board, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Abatement Board Correspondence, information sheets. Flyers and sign-up sheets for safety training.
- New York State Dept. of Labor -- Hazard Abatement Board, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Newspaper articles, information sheets.
- New York State Dept. of Labor -- Health and Safety Grant, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)